Bonowitz, Abraham J.; Papers apap186
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Communications, 1983-2013; 1; 2.6 cubic ft.
  - State Killing, Mennonite Central Committee Washington Office Guide to the Death Penalty, 2000 (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 5)
  - Stoppit!, Ohioans to Stop Executions Newsletter, 2005 (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 6)
  - Student Day Against the Death Penalty Handout, Undated (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 7)
  - Study Guide For the Documentary "Too Flawed to Fix: The Illinois Death Penalty Experience", ca. 2002 (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 8)
  - The Survivor, Survivors of Torture International, 2003 August; 2006 February (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 9)
  - S-Z Organization Pamphlets, Undated (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 10)
  - Take Action Not Lives, People of Faith Against the Death Penalty, 1998 (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 11)
  - Texas Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (TCADP) Newsletter, 2003 Summer/Fall; 2009; 2010 (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 12)
  - "Time For Death Penalty Moratorium is Past Due" by Abraham Bonowitz, The Tampa Tribune, 2000 December 23 (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 13)
  - The Time is Now, Illinois Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty Quarterly Newsletter, 2010 September (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 14)
  - The Torch, Newsletter of American Civil Liberties Union, 2006; 2007 (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 15)
  - A Taxpayers Guide to the California Death Penalty by Paul Comiskey, Undated (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 16)
  - A Tribute to Kentucky Abolitionists, KCADP Event Program, 2010 January 14 (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 17)
  - "Two Killer; One Spared" by John Seewer, The Associated Press, Undated (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 18)
  - Understanding Capital Punishment: A Guide Through the Death Penalty Debate, 2003 March (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 19)
  - "Unequal, Unfair and Irreversible, The Death Penalty in Virginia," American Civil Liberties Union of Virginia, 2000 April (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 20)
  - The University of Toledo Law Review, 2010 (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 21)
  - Virginians For Alternative to the Death Penalty (VADP) Action Newsletter, 2004 (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 22)
  - Virginians For Alternative to the Death Penalty 10th Anniversary Banquet Program, 2001 October 6 (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 23)
  - Virginians For Alternatives to the Death Penalty Event Program, 2008 June 25 (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 24)
  - The Vision, Religious Organizing Against the Death Penalty Project Newsletter, 2003 April; 2004 (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 25)
  - " The Voice" Special Report From the Healing the Wounds of Murder Conference, 2001 June (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 26)
  - Voices From California Crime Victims For Alternatives to the Death Penalty, 2008 January (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 27)
  - Voting While Incarcerated: A Toolkit For Advocates Seeking to Register, and Facilitate Voting by, Eligible People in Jail, 2005 September (Box 4 (1-Communications), Folder 1)
  - Washington Newsletter, Friends Committee on National Legislation, 2004 November; 2007 April (Box 4 (1-Communications), Folder 2)
  - "We on Death Row" United Colors of Benetton, 2000 January (Box 4 (1-Communications), Folder 3)
  - Where Justice and mercy Meet Catholic Opposition to the Death Penalty- Catholic Mobilizing Network, 2013 November (Box 4 (1-Communications), Folder 4)
  - "Why do We Tolerate Mistakes in Capital Punishment?" by Jane Eisner Dallas Morning News, 2003 May 26 (Box 4 (1-Communications), Folder 5)
  - Witness For Life, 2004; 2005; 2006 (Box 4 (1-Communications), Folder 6)
  - Witness to Innocence Newsletter, 2009 (Box 4 (1-Communications), Folder 7)
  - Witness, A Newsletter of the Fellowship of Reconciliation, 2005 (Box 4 (1-Communications), Folder 8)
  - World Coalition Against the Death Penalty Brochure, Undated (Box 4 (1-Communications), Folder 9)
  - World Day Against the Death Penalty, 2003-2004 (Box 4 (1-Communications), Folder 10)
  - The 2% Death Penalty: How a Minority of Counties Produce Most Death Cases at Enormous Cost to All, 2013 October (Box 4 (1-Communications), Folder 11)
  - 2nd World Congress Against the Death Penalty, Montreal 2004, 2004 October 6-9 (Box 4 (1-Communications), Folder 12)
  - 10.10 is A World Day, 10 years of World Coalition against the Death Penalty, 2012 (Box 4 (1-Communications), Folder 13)
  - 200 Exonerated Too Many Wrongfully Convicted, An Innocence Project Report on the First 200 DNA Exonerations in the U.S., Undated (Box 4 (1-Communications), Folder 14)
- Inmate Correspondence and Research, 1984-2015; 2; 2.2 cubic ft.
  This series contains articles, letters from inmates, reports about the death penalty, and summaries of cases. This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - "Abolition in the U.S.A by 2050: On Political Capital and Ordinary Acts of Resistance" by Bernard E. Harcourt, 2008 September (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 1)
  - Adams, James-Inmate Letter, 2005 July (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 2)
  - Anderson, Shermen-Inmate Letter, 2005 June 9 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 3)
  - Apanovitch, Anthony, 1994-1997; 2000; Undated (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 4)
  - Original Artwork by Ohio Death Row Prisoner Anthony C. Apanovitch and Legal Documents, Undated; 1994 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 5)
  - "The Application of the Death Penalty in New Mexico, July 1979 through December: 2007 An Empirical Analysis by Marcia J. Wilson, 2008 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 6)
  - Armstrong, Craigen-Inmare Letter, 2004 November 29 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 7)
  - Bandell, k-Inmate Letter, 2004 August 17 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 8)
  - Barrett, Clay-Inmate Letter, 2005 May 6 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 9)
  - "Battle Scars: Military Veterans and the Death Penalty: A Report by the Death Penalty Information Center", 2015 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 10)
  - Baze v. Rees-Question & Answer, Undated (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 11)
  - Bell Michael-Inmate Letter, 2007 March 22 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 12)
  - Bennett, Samuel-Inmate Letter, 2004 July 1 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 13)
  - Bishop, Alfred-Inmate Letter, 2003 December 24 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 14)
  - Blachwelder, John-Inmate Letter, 2003 August 21 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 15)
  - Bocskey, Terrence-Inmate Letter, 2005 February 18 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 16)
  - Bryant, Jeffrey-Inmate Letter, 2005 August 21 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 17)
  - Bryant, Rene James-Inmate Letter, 2004 June 14 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 18)
  - United States of America v. Brian Buckley, 2007 June 28 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 19)
  - Bults, Robert-Inmate Letter, 2004 September 13 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 20)
  - Carroll, Elmer-Inmate Letter, 2007 September (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 21)
  - Catholic Conference of Ohio Death Penalty Education, 2005 April (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 22)
  - Celebrating 25 of Fighting Injustice, Equal Justice USA 1990-2015 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 23)
  - Centurion Ministries Seeking Freedom of the Innocent in Prison, 2015 July (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 24)
  - Chamberlain, John-Inmate Letter, 2004 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 25)
  - Kenneth, Clair-Case Synopsis, Undated (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 26)
  - Clark, Larry-Inmate Letter, 2005 June 21 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 27)
  - Clark, Ronald-Inmate Letter, 2004 September 15 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 28)
  - Client Agency Agreement, The Rutherford Institute, 2013 June 19 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 29)
  - Colbert, John-Inmate Letter, 2007 September 17 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 30)
  - "The Collateral Ant. Therapeutic Effects of the Death Penalty" by Cynthia F. Adcock Florida Coastal Law Review, Undated (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 31)
  - Connick v. Thompson-Supreme Court of the United States-Cetiorari to the United States Court of Appeals for the fifth Cicuit Syllabus, 2010 October (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 32)
  - Copies of Inmate Letters, 2010 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 33)
  - Cook, Robert Jr. Inmate Letter, 2005 February 4 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 34)
  - Stop the Execution of Kevin Cooper- 1-Day Death Penalty Convergence, Undated (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 35)
  - Correa, David-Inmate Letter, 2007 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 36)
  - Cullen v. Pinhustler-Supreme Court of the United States-Certioran to the United States Court of Appeals for the Ninth Circuit, 2010 October (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 37)
  - Alan Davis v. State of Ohio-In the Court of Common Pleas, 2000 February 7 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 38)
  - Davis, Kenneth-Inmate Letter, 2006 April 25 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 39)
  - Davis, Troy- 2007 (1 of 3), Undated (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 40)
  - Davis, Troy- 2007 (2 of 3), Undated (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 41)
  - Davis, Troy- 2007 (3 of 3), Undated (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 42)
  - Davis, Troy v. Heed, Fredrick-Brief on Behalf of the Appellee, Undated (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 43)
  - State of Georgia, Troy Davis v. Tony Turpin, 1996 December 16 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 44)
  - Dawson, Adrian-Inmate Lettere, 2006 June 1 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 45)
  - Death Penalty and Resistance in Puerto Rico, Puerto Rico Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 2008 January (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 46)
  - The Death Penalty in the United States, Equal Justice USA, Undated (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 47)
  - The Death Penalty in 2008: Year End Report, 2008 December (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 48)
  - Doak, David-Inmate Letter, 2004 December 14 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 49)
  - Doolin, Keith Zon- Case Synopsis, Undated (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 50)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Service Program, 2014 January 19 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 51)
  - Draughun, Martin-Inmate Letter-Post Release, 2004 August 10 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 52)
  - Duckett, James-Inmate Letters, 2003 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 53)
  - Dufour-Don-Inmate Letter, 2004 February 3 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 54)
  - Esty, Seen-Inmate Letter, 2004 June 1 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 55)
  - "Execution's Doorstep: True Stories of the Innocent and Near Damned" by Leslie Lythe, 2008 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 56)
  - Exodus, Innocence Project of New Orleans, Undated (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 57)
  - "Facts about the Death Penalty" from the Death Penalty Information Center, 2014 November 15 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 58)
  - Field, Gary-Inmate Letter, 2005 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 59)
  - Flinner, Michael-Inmate Letter, 2005 July 6 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 60)
  - Flores, Charles-Inmate Letter, 2007 October 11 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 61)
  - Florida Coalition Against the Death Penalty and Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Penalty, 1984 June; 1999 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 62)
  - Floyd, James-Inmate Letter, 2005 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 63)
  - Ford, Latroy-Case Synopsis "Two Men Face the Death Penalty" by Kina Slutsky The Bradentor Herald, 2002 November 2 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 64)
  - Forlmpact Training, The Studdes Group, 2015 October 27-28 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 65)
  - Fralta, Robert-Inmate Letter, 2000 February 3 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 66)
  - "The Future of America's Death Penalty An Agenda For the Next Generation of Capital Punishment Research" edited by Chares S. Lanier William J. Bowers, James R. Acker, Carolina Academic Press, 2009 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 67)
  - "The Future of the Death Penalty in the U.S: A Texas-sized crisis" A Report by the Death Penalty Information Center, 1994 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 68)
  - Gabrion, Marvin-Inmate Letter, 2004 March 18 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 69)
  - Garcia, Antonio- Inmate Letter, Undated (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 70)
  - Garrison, Charles-Inmate Letter, 2006 July 17 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 71)
  - The Gathering: Exonerees Empowered to End the Death Penalty World Wide Conference, 2015 October 11 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 72)
  - Geffhen, Richard-Inmate Letter, 2004 April 26 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 73)
  - Gordon, Robert-Inmate Letter, 2004 August 17 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 74)
  - Grane, Lewis-Inmate Letter, Undated (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 75)
  - Gwynn, Daniel-Inmate Letter, 2004 August 24 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 76)
  - Haegrave,Christopher-Inmate Letter, 2005 February 18 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 77)
  - Hall, Carrie-Inmate Letter, 2010 August 9 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 78)
  - Harris,Roger-Inmate Letter, 2009 January 8 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 79)
  - Hawkins, David Lee-Inmate Letter, 2005 February 4 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 80)
  - Heid, John-Correspondence Concerning Death Row Inmate SuJour, Don, 2004 January 26 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 81)
  - Hendrix, Robert-Inmate Letter, 2005 March 31 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 82)
  - Hickox, Victor-Inmate Letter, 2006 September 22 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 83)
  - Hicks,William-Inmate Letter, 2007 May 30 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 84)
  - Hildwin, Paul-Inmate Letter Case Synopsis, 2003; Undated (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 85)
  - "How Abolition of the Death Penalty in North Carolina Could Improve Public Safety. Increase Opportunities and Build Prosperity" A policy Brief, 2010 April 30 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 86)
  - Huggins, John-Inmate Letter, 2004 August 20 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 87)
  - Human Rights Report, Southern Center for Human Rights Annual Newsletter, 2015 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 88)
  - Inmate Thank Yous for the donation of personal fans to Florida Death Row Inmate by CUADD, 2004 August (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 89)
  - Innocence: List of Those Freed from Death Row-Death Row Information Center, 2006 November 12 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 90)
  - "In Search of the Movement: 1960s Activist in labor" by Kim Fellner, 1989 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 91)
  - Johnson, Lorenzo-Inmate Letter, 2004 February 22 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 92)
  - Johnson, Marvin-Inmate Letter, 2004 September 29 (Box 1 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 93)
  - Johnston, David - Inmate Letter, 2004 August 1 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 1)
  - Judge Sabo's Death Row, Complied by Robert Brett Dunham, Director of Training, 2008 May 28 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 2)
  - Junior Scholastic Magazine Featuring Article "Cruel and Unusual? An Execution In Georgia Reignites Debate About Death Penalty", 2001 November 21 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 3)
  - Johnson, Roderick - Inmate Letter, 2007 December 26 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 5)
  - Kelley, William - Inmate Letters (1 of 2), 2003-2008; Undated (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 6)
  - Kelley, William - Inmate Letters (2 of 2), 2003-2008; Undated (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 7)
  - Kelley, William v. Secretary of the Florida Department of Corrections - Petition for Writ of Certiorari, Undated (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 8)
  - King, James - Inmate Letter, 2006 november 1 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 9)
  - Krane, Ray - A Death Row Exoneree Biography, Undated (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 10)
  - Lambrix, Michael - Inmate Letter, 2010 July 7 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 11)
  - Langon, Steve - Inmate Letter, 2006 December 8 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 12)
  - Laryarca, Anthony - Inmate Letter, 2005 July 11 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 13)
  - Leane, Madonna - Inmate Letter, 2004 August 11 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 14)
  - "Lethal Rejection: Democracy, Meet Philadelphia" by Matthew Domer, 1996 June 26 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 15)
  - Lewis, Reginald - Inmate Letter, 2004 November 22 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 16)
  - "Life Without Parole, Our Other Death Penalty" by Johnson, Robert, 2006 October 22 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 17)
  - Lovlace, Faron - Inmate Letter, 2004 July 30 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 18)
  - Lowe, Rodney - Inmate Letter, 2005 December 12 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 19)
  - Manning, Sherman - Inmate Letter Undated (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 20)
  - Marack, Troy - Inmate Letter, 2007 June 26 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 21)
  - Mandatory Justice Eighteen Reforms to the Death Penalty, 2001 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 22)
  - Matthews, M.D. - Inmate Letter, 2006 October 18 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 23)
  - McKinron, Crandell - Inmate Letter, 2007 October 31 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 24)
  - Media, Tony - Inmate Letter, 2007 August 23 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 25)
  - Melendez, Juan, 2004; Undated (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 26)
  - Mental Illness Initiative, Death Penalty Due Process Review Project, 2015 September 21 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 27)
  - Miceli, Charles - Inmate Letter, 2004 June 3 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 28)
  - Michaels, Bruce - Inmate Letter, 2004 March 25 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 29)
  - Mississippi Death Row, 2007; Undated (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 30)
  - "Money For Nothing? The Financial Cost of New Jersey's Death Penalty" by Many, E. Forsberg, New Jersey Policy Perspective, 2005 November (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 31)
  - Mordenti, Michael - Inmate Letters, 2005 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 32)
  - Moratorium Now - A Campaign of Equal Justice USA, 2005 August (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 33)
  - New Jersey Death Penalty Study Commission Report, 2007 January (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 34)
  - Norton, Dwayne Jay - Inmate Letter, 2004 April 19 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 35)
  - Pachero, John - Inmate Letter, 2004 March 28 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 36)
  - Pearce, Faurce - Inmate Letter, 2005 October 16 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 37)
  - "A Perspective from Death Row: The Case of Exonerated Inmate, Glenn Ford", 2015 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 38)
  - "Persuasion Messaging, and Messangers: How New Jersey Replaced the Death Penalty with Life Without Parole" A Master's Paper in Community Psychology and Social Change by Andrew J. Hoover, 2008 August (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 39)
  - Porter, George - Inmate Letter, 2004 September 4 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 40)
  - Prince, Wayne - Inmate Letter, 2006 June 11 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 41)
  - Reinder Folmer, Corry P., 1994 May 25 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 42)
  - Responses of Members of Murder Victims' Families for the Concept of Restitution - Implications and Suggestions for Legislation in Lieu of Capital Punishment - by Friedman- Barone, Ronnie, 2000 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 43)
  - Lawrence Reynold v. Ted Strickel and et. al. - United States Court of Appeals, 2009 October 5 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 44)
  - Reyos, James Harry - Inmate Letter, 2004 October 12 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 45)
  - Riley, William David - Inmate Letter, 2005 June 9 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 46)
  - Rivera, Michael - Inmate Letter, 2005 January 6 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 47)
  - Romero, Edwin - Inmate Letter, 2004 March 20 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 48)
  - Rose, Milo - Inmate Letter, 2003 October 24 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 49)
  - Rosemond, A.K. - Inmate Letter, 2000 May 5 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 50)
  - Rosenburg Fund for Children - Year End Report, 2015 December 8 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 51)
  - Ross, Michael - Inmate Letters, 2005; Undated (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 52)
  - Rowell, Don - Inmate Letter, 2008 April 15 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 53)
  - Schwab, Mark Dean - Execution Date, 2007 July 18 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 54)
  - "Secondary Trauma Associated with State Executions: Testimony Regarding Execution Procedures" by Amanda Gil, Matthew B. Johnson, and Ingrid Johnson, Journal of Psychiatry and Law, 2006 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 55)
  - "Sentencing for Life: Americans Embrace Alternatives to the Death Penalty" A Report by the Death Penalty Information Center, 1993 April (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 56)
  - Selts, Burt - Inmate Letter, 2006 April 8 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 57)
  - Sheldon, Jeff - Inmate Letter, 2005 July (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 58)
  - Shelton, Herman - Inmate Letter, 2004 February 17 (Box 2 (2-Inmate Correspondence and Research), Folder 59)